Now we know pretty much everything we need to know to actually get into the recipe.
现在我们几乎知道了真正进入食谱需要知道的一切。
Let's first talk about the ingredients we need to make stir fried tomato and eggs a classic Chinese
先来说说番茄炒鸡蛋成为经典中式需要的食材
dish which actually I really enjoy making something I can actually make to make stir fried tomato and
这道菜实际上我真的很喜欢做一些我可以做的东西来做炒番茄和
eggs you will need three eggs or more if you prefer to chopped and peeled tomatoes some people slice
鸡蛋 如果您喜欢切碎和去皮的西红柿，您将需要三个或更多鸡蛋有些人切片
them some people cut them into wedges sesame oil salt sugar olive oil and scallions you can add diced
他们有些人把它们切成楔形芝麻油盐糖橄榄油和葱你可以加入丁
Ginger if you like.
喜欢的话生姜。
So that's an option.
所以这是一个选择。
It's an optional thing.
这是一个可选的东西。
Also you'll need steamed rice on the side.
你还需要一边蒸米饭。
OK so we're not going to actually add that to the walk to the pan but we will need it when we actually
好的，所以我们实际上不会将它添加到步行到锅中，但是当我们真正需要它时
eat it.
吃了它。
So I have steamed rice on the side.
所以我一边蒸米饭。
So these are the ingredients.
所以这些是成分。
This is what we need to actually prepare our dish.
这是我们实际准备菜肴所需要的。
Now let's get into the recipe itself.
现在让我们进入食谱本身。
So we're going to add two tablespoons of olive oil into a pre heated walk.
所以我们要在预热的步道中加入两汤匙橄榄油。
Remember that's a kind of pan and wait for the oil to heat up next.
请记住，这是一种平底锅，然后等待油加热。
Add diced scallions to kind of it's like an onion.
加入葱末，有点像洋葱。
And when you smell the aroma of the scallions Beat the eggs Beat the eggs and pour them into the pan.
当你闻到大葱的香气时 打鸡蛋 打鸡蛋，倒入锅中。
Once they are almost fully cooked pour them back into the mixing bowl.
一旦它们几乎完全煮熟，将它们倒回搅拌碗中。
So that's really step one after we take the eggs and we pour them into the mixing bowl again.
所以这真的是我们取鸡蛋并再次将它们倒入搅拌碗中的第一步。
Now the walk is probably cool.
现在步行可能很酷。
So we need to reheated so reheat the pan and add another tablespoon of olive oil.
所以我们需要重新加热，所以重新加热锅，再加一汤匙橄榄油。
If you're using Ginger if you're using Ginger add that then immediately add the tomatoes and cook them
如果你用的是生姜，如果你用的是生姜，那就加那个，然后立即加入西红柿煮熟
until they start turning golden brown.
直到它们开始变成金黄色。
OK.
好的。
So that's the condition we're not going to use time.
这就是我们不使用时间的条件。
We're going to use a description instead of saying this many minutes because maybe you're cooking on
我们将使用描述而不是说这么多分钟，因为也许你正在做饭
a higher or lower temperature until they start turning golden brown then put in the sesame oil a tablespoon
更高或更低的温度，直到它们开始变成金黄色，然后放入一汤匙芝麻油
of sugar.
糖。
That's a measurement of sugar a tablespoon of sugar and a few pinches of salt to taste.
这是糖的量度，一汤匙糖和几撮盐调味。
If you add something to taste that means basically you add it until it's enough for you.
如果你添加一些东西来调味，这基本上意味着你添加它直到它对你来说足够了。
Some people like saltier food.
有些人喜欢吃咸的食物。
Some people like food that's less salty.
有些人喜欢少咸的食物。
So add it according to what you like add a few pinches of salt to taste.
所以根据你的喜好添加它，加几撮盐调味。
Finally add the eggs into the walk and stir fry for another two minutes.
最后将鸡蛋加入步道中，再翻炒两分钟。
So now we want to use time because we want to make sure we don't overcook the tomatoes or overcooked
所以现在我们要利用时间，因为我们要确保西红柿不会煮过头或煮过头
the eggs.
鸡蛋。
We're going to cook only for two minutes more.
我们只多煮两分钟。
Stir fry for another two minutes.
再翻炒两分钟。
OK.
好的。
And then it's done.
然后就完成了。
Basically we could say add the eggs back into the walk.
基本上我们可以说将鸡蛋加回步行中。
You could say back because they've been in before and you could say stir fry for two minutes or until
你可以回复，因为他们以前来过，你可以说翻炒两分钟或直到
and then you could make a description if you want to do that.
然后你可以做一个描述，如果你想这样做。
That way you want to make sure it's not overcooked.
这样你要确保它没有煮过头。
So for example if you say or until the tomatoes start getting very soft.
因此，例如，如果您说或直到西红柿开始变软。
So in other words if they start getting very soft before two minutes then take everything out.
所以换句话说，如果他们在两分钟前开始变得非常柔软，那就把所有东西都拿出来。
Sometimes having two instructions a time or a description can make sure something that you don't want
有时一次有两个指令或一个描述可以确保你不想要的东西
to happen doesn't happen.
发生不会发生。
Finally turn off the heat and let it cool for five minutes.
最后关火，让它冷却五分钟。
Serve over steamed white rice.
上蒸白米饭。
OK.
好的。
So just turn it off that means turn off the burner.
所以只要把它关掉就意味着关掉b瓮。
We can sometimes call that a burner and just leave it there.
我们有时可以将其称为燃烧器，然后将其留在那里。
Don't touch it.
不要碰它。
Then after five minutes can put it on top of steamed rice when we serve something over something then
然后五分钟后可以把它放在蒸米饭上，当我们把东西放在东西上的时候
we don't mix it in.
我们不会把它混进去。
You don't want to mix it into the rice.
你不想把它混进米饭里。
Here's the white rice.
这是白米饭。
Here's the tomato and egg on top of it.
这是上面的番茄和鸡蛋。
And then people can sort of mix it as they're eating it if they want to or not.
然后人们可以在他们吃的时候混合它，如果他们愿意的话。
That's the difference between mixing things in and serving over hopefully at the end of this lesson
这就是在本课结束时将东西混合和希望服务之间的区别
you feel more comfortable talking about food and how to prepare it in English at the beginning we talked
在我们开始讨论的时候，你觉得用英语谈论食物和如何准备食物会更自在
about cuisine and how we can describe our feelings about cuisine.
关于美食以及我们如何描述我们对美食的感受。
Some common cooking actions and some useful phrases and then we actually looked at a real recipe including
一些常见的烹饪动作和一些有用的短语，然后我们实际上查看了一个真实的食谱，包括
the ingredients that we need for that recipe.
我们制作该食谱所需的成分。
Now to practice this what I'd like you to do is write down a recipe describe a recipe in detail.
现在练习这个我想让你做的是写下一个食谱详细描述一个食谱。
Talk about the ingredients and all of the actions the amounts and then give it to a friend and see if
谈论成分和所有行动的数量，然后把它交给朋友，看看是否
it comes out OK Have them make it and then maybe go over to their house and see if your description
结果是好的让他们成功然后也许去他们家看看你的描述是否
of the dish actually worked.
这道菜实际上奏效了。
Remember to do it only in English.
记住只用英语做。
That's a real test of how well you're able to describe a particular food that you know how to cook.
这是一个真正的考验，你能够描述一种你知道如何烹饪的特定食物。
So good luck with that and I will see you in the next lesson.
祝你好运，我们下节课见。